<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Decision Making on Mikaël Gibert</title><link>https://migibert.github.io/tags/decision-making/</link><description>Recent content in Decision Making on Mikaël Gibert</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.156.0</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://migibert.github.io/tags/decision-making/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aligning Priorities Across Teams in a Large, Distributed Company</title><link>https://migibert.github.io/posts/management/team-performance/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://migibert.github.io/posts/management/team-performance/</guid><description>Learn how to align priorities across teams in a large, distributed company using structured decision-making frameworks. Discover how to identify and resolve conflicting priorities, make explicit trade-offs, and ensure conscious, data-driven decisions. Improve cross-team collaboration, prevent accidental prioritization, and create a clear roadmap for success.</description></item><item><title>From ODR to CSP: Optimizing Decision-Making with Timefold</title><link>https://migibert.github.io/posts/decision-records/odr-csp/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://migibert.github.io/posts/decision-records/odr-csp/</guid><description>Learn how to optimize decision-making by transforming an Organization Decision Record (ODR) into a Constraint Satisfaction Problem (CSP) using Timefold. This guide walks through modeling constraints, implementing a solver, and automating complex team assignments with AI-driven optimization.</description></item><item><title>ODR: Decision-making made simple</title><link>https://migibert.github.io/posts/decision-records/odr-intro/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://migibert.github.io/posts/decision-records/odr-intro/</guid><description>Discover how the Organization Decision Record (ODR) framework simplifies complex decision-making by structuring context, constraints, and options. Learn a practical approach to documenting and streamlining organizational decisions effectively.</description></item></channel></rss>